[{"answer": "Well, as a matter of fact, Piers, that's an excellent observation.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Is it that, do you think, that is drawing so much attention?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, this is my feeling on the death penalty -- there are certain cases that are so heinous that option should be offered to a jury.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "I mean, would you advocate the death penalty in this case, Nancy?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, he'll face a trial unless his lawyers plea bargain.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Do you think we're going to see John Edwards facing a trial for which he could be convicted here?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "That's certainly what the prosecution is going to argue here.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "So, in that sense, it is a donation to help him politically, isn't it?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's right.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Is it as clear cut as that do you think?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I think that's a legitimate question.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Has this decision been taken for political reasons, do you think?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I think -- yes, it is something I've heard.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Do people say that to you?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Did it say that?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "I mean, do you see yourself as a sex siren?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "I don't hate it.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "Do you hate it?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "You know, the worst thing about it is saying the number.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "What's the worst thing about it?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "I mean, no spark?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes, it does.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Does it make you laugh now when you think back to that?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "It makes me laugh now, but I do have to say there were 10 years between the age of 15 and maybe 25 that it didn't make me laugh.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Awfully satisfying, isn't it?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Because they completely crushed me.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "You could look at it that way.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "You're having the last laugh, aren't you?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I like them because, first of all, I don't think I'm supposed to be turned on.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "And why, Ellen?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I mean, I don't know how I'd feel about it now.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Yes, of course.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Could you imagine doing a scene like that now?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "No reason, no.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "It helps when it's Dennis Quaid.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Does it help when you've got some hunk like Dennis Quaid?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "That is so unfair.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Who's the sexiest man you've ever done a scene with of any kind?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "And we had a very graphic sex scene.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Was he really?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Tell me about your ex because you have a very nice ex- husband relationship, don't you?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, we're both very sane people, I think.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "How have you managed to do it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "We had a wonderful eight, ten years together.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Is it unthinkable that you two could get back together?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Many?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "A lot of people?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "The battle is not being won, which is why I'm so proud to be a part of this play now, because I think it's more important than ever that people are reminded there is no cure.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Do you think that's the case?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Something so passionate, so visceral, has such an amazing connection with an audience night-after-night.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "And I think, you know, what's there not to get angry about?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Sometimes it is, and sometimes it isn't.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "How can you go from that to a movie set, doing something that will inevitably be so trivial by comparison?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "It's called \"Another Happy Day.\"", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "What is that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "On the whole, I'd rather be in Philadelphia?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I remember Jim punching the wall behind me and being a little bit concerned for my well being.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "What do you think when you see that?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Life has turned out so differently for me than I originally thought it would.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Why have you never been a wife?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "How did you imagine your life would look?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I couldn't tell you.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "Do you think you'll ever get married one day?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "What's happening right now.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Would you like to?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "No, actually I don't, in all honesty.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "When you see friends who are married, do you envy them or not?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "There's not much left with the bleeps, truth be told.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Actually, my situation was very different from her.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "But when you played the role, how much was absolutely you when you were going through addiction?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "It was alcohol, yeah.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Yours was just alcohol?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "I don't actually.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Do you ever miss alcohol?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Is that part of the way you win these things?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Do you like doing interviews?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "You're doing just fine.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "What's happening now?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I am far worse than you know.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Why are you blocking your ears?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "No, it's -- you know, I like to believe that -- I can never hear myself the way I appear to other people, hear or see myself.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Is that what this all comes down to, that your life is never going to be right for you?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "A person I've gotten to know very well.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "When you look in the mirror, what do you see?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "Very much so, yeah.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Do you like her?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "You know, had I not had the whatever, wherewithal, gumption to quit drinking -- I have a highly addictive personality.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "if things had followed a different path for you, when you think about the worst case scenario, where could you have ended up?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Absolutely, it is.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "Is that what it's like for you?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "For sure.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Are you miles more confident like many performers when you're on a stage?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "I like the mix up of it.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 725, "question": "Do you wish you could sometimes have that confidence in real life?", "qSentId": 724}, {"answer": "Oh, my heavens.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "I am, for sure.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Are you as happy now as you've ever been?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "Have you thought about your speech?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "No, I really, haven't.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "If you win?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Yes, I have no -- I don't -- I have no idea.", "docId": "110603pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 751}]